<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Nived.</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m Nived.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m Nived P A, currently a final year undergraduate at Amrita University majoring in Computer Science and Engineering with specialization in Artificial Intelligence. I’m also a part of the Machine Learning team at AfterShoot where we build software for professional photographers to automate their workflow.
Experiences AfterShoot Inc. (November 2021 - Present) At AfterShoot we make software for professional photographers to automate their workflow. We use Computer Vision and Machine Learning algorithms to perform photo culling, which involves selection of the desirable photos from a large group based on characteristics such as blur, duplicates, emotions, face sharpness and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://example.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>Academic Projects List of projects I have completed as a part of various courses taken in college.
Classification and Diagnosis of COVID-19 from Medical Images (May 2021)
Implemented a supervised Convolutional Neural Network for classification of medical images for detecting the presence of Covid/Pneumonia affected lung images. We noticed that the models used for similar purposes at the time only worked with good accuracy on the training datasets, whereas on a different dataset that contained similar CT Scan images the accuracy was reduced to 60-70%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
